<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-06-27T22:13:34+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Book Keeper’s Archive</title><subtitle>Logs and dossiers of all known teams, including restricted and inactive groups.</subtitle><author><name>The Book Keeper</name></author><entry><title type="html">A Memory of Strixhaven</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/strixhaven/1.%20remembering%20strixhaven/2025/06/27/prologue_to_strixhaven/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Memory of Strixhaven" /><published>2025-06-27T14:30:00+02:00</published><updated>2025-06-27T14:30:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/strixhaven/1.%20remembering%20strixhaven/2025/06/27/prologue_to_strixhaven</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/strixhaven/1.%20remembering%20strixhaven/2025/06/27/prologue_to_strixhaven/"><![CDATA[<p>I can’t remember why I chose to enroll in Strixhaven. Was it the allure of magic, the gathering of so many people in one place, or was it something else entirely? Lately, I’ve been thinking back to that time, which feels like a lifetime ago. I remember writing everything down back then. I hope to recover every single note of my youth, including this one—though I fear they are lost in the void. For now, I will write down everything I can recall.</p>]]></content><author><name>The Book Keeper</name></author><category term="strixhaven" /><category term="1. Remembering Strixhaven" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can’t remember why I chose to enroll in Strixhaven. Was it the allure of magic, the gathering of so many people in one place, or was it something else entirely? Lately, I’ve been thinking back to that time, which feels like a lifetime ago. I remember writing everything down back then. I hope to recover every single note of my youth, including this one—though I fear they are lost in the void. For now, I will write down everything I can recall.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Prologue to the Murkmire Malevolence 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/team_14/01%20-%20murkmire%20malevolence/2025/06/13/the_murkmire_malevolence/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Prologue to the Murkmire Malevolence 1" /><published>2025-06-13T23:30:00+02:00</published><updated>2025-06-13T23:30:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/team_14/01%20-%20murkmire%20malevolence/2025/06/13/the_murkmire_malevolence</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/team_14/01%20-%20murkmire%20malevolence/2025/06/13/the_murkmire_malevolence/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="members">Members</h2>
<p><a href="/team_14/caelum">#1. Caelum</a></p>

<p><a href="/team_14/amber">#2. Amber</a></p>

<p><a href="/team_14/rowan">#3. Rowan</a></p>

<p><a href="/team_14/grof_granok">#4. Grof</a></p>

<p><a href="/team_14/alice">#5 Alice</a></p>

<h2 id="logs">Logs</h2>

<h3 id="rise-team-14">Rise team 14</h3>
<p><em>15th of Ches, 1493DR</em></p>

<p>Today I assembled a new team (team 14) to replace team 11. A group of random loners. A prince who will never sit on his father’s throne, a rogue with no family name (yet) who was forced to live in the shadows (but was not hard to find), a druid, a barbarian, and… should they get bored, a bard to entertain them. I estimate their chances of success at 23%. Tomorrow I will meet them.</p>

<h3 id="the-stone-that-is-an-egg">The stone that is an egg</h3>
<p><em>16th of Ches, 1493DR[I]</em></p>

<p>A doctor at Varkenbluff University in Greyhawk has approached me. Like many who are desperate, she offered me gold to help her. Her story intrigued me. A stone that is not a stone but an egg — that reminds me of one of the members of team 14, but I digress… The doctor claims it is the egg of an eldritch horror. If it hatches, it could have dire consequences, and time is of the essence. Since urgency is required, I fear there is no choice but to assign team 14 to the task. Well, if we do nothing, the outcome may be worse… I hope.</p>

<h3 id="a-somwhat-not-horrible-first-meeting">A somwhat not horrible first meeting</h3>
<p><em>16th of Ches, 1493DR[II]</em></p>

<p>My loyal assistant #237 (rest in peace #236) has brought team 14 to me. It felt awkward, as if some of them had never been part of a group before. I am starting to have doubts about this group’s chances of success. <a href="./grof_granok.md">#4</a> is a typical barbarian who prefers fighting over careful strategies. <a href="./alice.md">#5</a> is not a bard as you would expect. No eye contact whatsoever. <a href="./caelum.md">#1</a> carries a purple glowing stone, which he believes is well hidden. <a href="./rowan.md">#3</a> showed his discomfort—whether this was due to the group or because he cannot cope with the bustle of the city I have yet to discover. <a href="./amber.md">#2</a> has piqued my interest. Usually, I can quickly uncover a contractor’s background, but with this halfling I have not succeeded so far.</p>

<p>I have instructed them to speak with Doctor Darnell. #237 will bring them to her. To be sure, I am sending [redacted] along to keep an eye on them.</p>]]></content><author><name>The Book Keeper</name></author><category term="team_14" /><category term="01 - Murkmire Malevolence" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Members #1. Caelum #2. Amber #3. Rowan #4. Grof #5 Alice Logs Rise team 14 15th of Ches, 1493DR Today I assembled a new team (team 14) to replace team 11. A group of random loners. A prince who will never sit on his father’s throne, a rogue with no family name (yet) who was forced to live in the shadows (but was not hard to find), a druid, a barbarian, and… should they get bored, a bard to entertain them. I estimate their chances of success at 23%. Tomorrow I will meet them. The stone that is an egg 16th of Ches, 1493DR[I] A doctor at Varkenbluff University in Greyhawk has approached me. Like many who are desperate, she offered me gold to help her. Her story intrigued me. A stone that is not a stone but an egg — that reminds me of one of the members of team 14, but I digress… The doctor claims it is the egg of an eldritch horror. If it hatches, it could have dire consequences, and time is of the essence. Since urgency is required, I fear there is no choice but to assign team 14 to the task. Well, if we do nothing, the outcome may be worse… I hope. A somwhat not horrible first meeting 16th of Ches, 1493DR[II] My loyal assistant #237 (rest in peace #236) has brought team 14 to me. It felt awkward, as if some of them had never been part of a group before. I am starting to have doubts about this group’s chances of success. #4 is a typical barbarian who prefers fighting over careful strategies. #5 is not a bard as you would expect. No eye contact whatsoever. #1 carries a purple glowing stone, which he believes is well hidden. #3 showed his discomfort—whether this was due to the group or because he cannot cope with the bustle of the city I have yet to discover. #2 has piqued my interest. Usually, I can quickly uncover a contractor’s background, but with this halfling I have not succeeded so far. I have instructed them to speak with Doctor Darnell. #237 will bring them to her. To be sure, I am sending [redacted] along to keep an eye on them.]]></summary></entry></feed>